Finding Aid for the Collection of 78rpm Sound Discs PASC-M.0174
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Ken Stone Gift, Series 7.
  - 10-inch collection, Subseries 1.
    - Johnny Dodds: The King of New Orleans Clarinets, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: B-1020
    - Let's Dance with Benny Goodman, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: P-188
    - Louis Armstrong Classics: New Orleans to New York, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: A-572
    - Mezz Mezzrow and Tommy Ladnier: Vol. 2
      Publisher no.: VLP 204
      Artists: Mezz Mezzrow, Tommy Ladnier, Sidney Bechet, Max Kaminsky, Benny Carter, Sidney de Paris, Floyd O'Brien, Teddy Wilson, James P. Johnson, Cliff Jackson, Pops Foster, Teddy Bunn, Zutty Singleton.
    - Musical comedy favorites, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: Set M-430
    - New Orleans Rhythm Kings featuring George Brunis, 5024
    - Ridin' Herd!
      Publisher no.: CL 2509
    - Riverboat Jazz: New Orleans to Chicago, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: B-1010
      Artists: King Oliver's Dixie Syncopators, Dewey Jackson's Peacock Orchestra, Jelly Roll Morton's Levee Serenaders, Jimmy Wade & His Dixielander with Punch Miller, Albert Wynn's Gut Bucket Five, Albert Wynn's Creole Jazz Band with Punch Miller.
    - Sidney Bechet
      Publisher no.: MG 15013
    - Sidney Bechet and his New Orleans Feetwarmers: Vol. 2
      Publisher no.: 5028
    - Sidney Bechet and his New Orleans Feetwarmers: Vol. 1
      Publisher no.: 5027
    - Sidney Bechet: Vol. 1
      Publisher no.: 1801
    - Singing the Blues, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: P-192
      Artists: Louis Armstron, Mildred Bailey, Jack Teagarden, Ethel Waters
    - St. Louis Woman [Cover], 5 discs
      VARIOUS DISCS INSIDE, not from St. Louis Woman. Jelly-Roll Morton's New Orleans Jazzmen, Max Kaminsky and His Jazz Band, Bessie Smith, Santo "Peck" Pecora and his Backroom Boys, Bennie Goodman's Boys.
    - Teddy Wilson, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: C-93
    - Tesch: Chicago Style Clarinetist, 4 discs
      Publisher no.: B-1017
      Artists: Frank Teschemacher, Muggsy Spanier, Wingy Manone, Red McKenzie, Eddie Condon, Gene Krupa, George Wettling, Milt Mezzrow, Bud Freeman, Joe Sullivan, Art Hodes.
    - The B.G. Six
      Publisher no.: CL 2564
    - The Man with a Horn, 1949; 3 discs
      Publisher no.: A-719
      Artists: Randy Brooks, Bobby Hackett, Louis Armstrong, Roy Eldridge, Butterfield, Muggsy Spanier
    - The Voice of Frank Sinatra [Cover], 4 discs
    - Tommy Dorsey's Clambake Seven
      Publisher no.: P-220
    - Two-Beat
      Publisher no.: CL2505
    - You, and the Night, and the Music...by Tony Martin [cover], 4 discs
      Artists: George Hartman and his Orchestra, Max Kaminsky and His Jazz Band, Tommy Dorsey and his Orchestra, Chick Webb and his Orchestra,
    - Assorted Unprocessed Commercial Sound Discs (Box 732)
      Albums in Box 732
    - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 972)
    - Art Tatum Trio
      Publisher no.: BL 58013
  - 12-inch collection, Subseries 2.
    - Five Feet of Swing, 5 discs
      Publisher no.: Album No. 131
      Artists: Bob Crosby, Jimmy Dorsey, Dorsey Brothers, Glenn Gray, Chick Webb.
    - Louis Armstrong All Stars with Jack Teagarden, 3 discs
      Publisher no.: HJ-14
    - Mary Lou Williams, 3 discs
      Publisher no.: 1005-1007
    - Porgy and Bess, 3 out of 4 discs present
      Publisher no.: Album no. 145
  - 10-inch Ken Stone Gift, no cover, Subseries 3.
    Recordex Collection
    - Roll On, Mississippi, Roll On [Side A] -- Shout, Sister Shout! [Side B], 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: B-1003
    - Bessie Couldn't Help It [Side A] -- Barnacle Bill, The Sailor [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 532
    - Kissing Bug-Fox Trot [Side A] -- Mood to Be Wooed-Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 20-1670
      [Side A] Vocal Refrain by Joya Sherrill -- [Side B] Featuring Johnny Hodges on the Saxophone.
    - Don't Get Around Much Anymore- Fox Trot [Side A]; Cotton Tail- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 26610
    - I Found a New Baby- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Flying Home- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 36721, C-102
    - S.O.L. Blues-Fox Trot [Side A] -- Squeeze Me [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: C-28; 35661
    - Passion Flower-Fox Trot [Side A] -- Going Out The Back Way- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: 30-0817
    - Martha: Ah So Pure ("M'appari tutt' amor") [Side A] -- Home on the Range [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: 1600
    - Where the Blues were Born in New Orleans [Side A] -- Mahagony Hall Stomp [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 20-2088
    - Royal Garden Blues [Side A] -- How Long Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: C101; 36710
    - Stop the War- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Mama's Gone, Good-bye -Fox Trot {Side B] (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: B-11107
    - Thou Swell [Side A] -- Louisiana [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: C-24; 35665
    - I'll Get Mine Bye and Bye [Side A], Yes Suh! [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 3900
    - 2:19 Blues (Mamie's Blues) [Side A] -- Perdido Street Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 18090
      Album no. 144 (12 sides-2)
    - Red River Blues [Side A] -- I Need You [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 14326-D
    - Doctor Jazz- Stomp [Side A] -- Memphis Shake- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 20415
    - The Moochie- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Blues in the Air- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 20-1510
    - Swing Paradise- Fox Trot [Side A] -- I Know That You Know- Fox Trot [Side B], cracked (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: 27574
    - At the Christmas Ball [Side A] -- Preachin' the Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: 35842
    - Baby Won't You Please Come Home [Side A] -- Shanty Boat on the Mississippi [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: 2729
    - King Porter Stomp [Side A] -- All Star Strut [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 35389
    - Changes- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Deep Down South- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 25370
    - St. Louis Shuffle [Side A] -- Variety Stomp [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: B-10246
    - Sugar [Side A] -- The World is Waiting for the Sunrise [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: 18043
    - China Boy [Side A] -- Jazz Me Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 25)
      Publisher no.: 18042
    - Orifinal Dixieland One Step (Original Dixieland Jazz Band) [Side A] -- I'm All Bound 'Round With the Mason Dixon Line [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 26)
      Publisher no.: 18441
    - Bugle Call Rag [Side A] -- I Wish I Could Shimmy Like My Sister Kate [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Publisher no.: 18044
    - There'll Be Some Changes Made [Side A] -- Someday, Sweetheart [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 28)
      Publisher no.: 18041
    - I Want A Little Girl [Side A] -- Blues For Yesterday [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 29)
      Publisher no.: SW 223
    - Melancholy [Side A] -- Wildman Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Publisher no.: 580.003
    - On the Sunny Side of the Street (1re partie)[Side A] -- On the Sunny Side of the Street (2me partie)[Side B] (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Publisher no.: 580.010
    - After You've Gone- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Man from the South- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 32)
      Publisher no.: R 607
      New Rhythm Style Series, No. 25
    - You Don't Learn That In School [Side A] -- I Believe [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Publisher no.: 20-2240
    - Basin Street Blues- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Some Sweet Day- Fox Trot [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 34)
      Publisher no.: K-8152
    - After You've Gone- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Dark Eyes (Box 1, Folder 35)
      Publisher no.: 38147
    - Saint-Louis Blues [Side A] -- Tiger Rag [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 36)
      Publisher no.: 580.002
    - Make Believe- Medley Fox Trot (Introduction, "Old Pal, Why Don't You Answer Me?") [Side A] -- Some Little Song Bird-- Medley Fox Trot (Introducing, "The Mocking Bird") [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 37)
      Publisher no.: 18742
    - Jack-Armstrong Blues (Louis Armstrong-Jack Teagarden) [Side A] -- Rockin' Chair [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Publisher no.: 20-2348
    - Song of the Vipers [Side A] -- Will You Won't You Be My Baby [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 39)
      Publisher no.: 580.041
    - Beau Koo Jack [Side A] -- No One Else But You [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Publisher no.: 279.621
    - Fireworks- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Saint James Informary [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 41)
      Publisher no.: 279.711
    - Bessie Couldn't Keep It [Side A] -- Dallas Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 42)
      Publisher no.: 279.485
    - So Little Tims (So Much To Do) [Side A] -- Mexican Swing [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 43)
      Publisher no.: 1822
    - Stardust- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Wrap Your Troubles in Dreams (And Dream Your Troubles Away) [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 44)
      Publisher no.: 37808
    - Skip The Gutter [Side A] -- Knee Drop [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 45)
      Publisher no.: 165.578
    - West End Blues [Side A] -- Dinah [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 46)
      Publisher no.: 279.742
    - You're Driving Me Crazy [Side A] -- The Peanut Vendor [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 47)
      Publisher no.: 238.404
    - Countin' the Blues [Side A] -- Jelly Bean Blues [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 48)
      Publisher no.: U.H.C.A. No. 84
      Accompaniment featuring: Louis Armstrong- Cornet, Charlie Green- Trombone, Buster Bailey- Clarinet
    - I've Got a Crush on You [Side A] -- Penthouse Serenade [Side B] (Box 1, Folder 49)
      Publisher no.: 505
    - King Porter- Fox Trot [Side A] -- Sometimes I'm Happy [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Publisher no.: 25090
    - I Wonder [Side A] -- Jodie Man [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Publisher no.: 186552
    - I Can't Give You Anything but Love, Baby [Side A] -- Fiesta in Blue [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Publisher no.: 36755
    - Back O'Town Blues [Side A] -- Linger in My Arms A Little Longer, Baby [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Publisher no.: 20-1912
    - Girl of My Dreams [Side A] -- Rainbow Blues [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Publisher no.: 500
    - More Than You Know [Side A] -- Sugar (That Sugar Baby O'Mine) [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Publisher no.: 36117
    - That Da Da Strain [Side A] -- Someday Sweetheart [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Publisher no.: B-10384
    - Relaxin' at the Touro [Side A] -- Riverboat Shuffle [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Publisher no.: B-10532
    - Jazz Me Blues [Side A] -- There'll Be Some Changes Made [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Publisher no.: 26244
    - Solo Flight [Side A] -- The World is Waiting for the Sunrise [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Publisher no.: 36684
    - Somebody Loves Me [Side A] -- Jam Session [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Publisher no.: 25497
    - After You've Gone [Side A] -- Body and Soul [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 12)
      Publisher no.: 36781
    - Sweet Sue-Just You [Side A] -- My Meloncholy Baby [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 13)
      Publisher no.: 25473
    - After You've Gone [Side A] -- At the Darktown Strutters' Ball [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 14)
      Publisher no.: 36699
    - No Variety Blues [Side A] -- What Ya Gonna Do [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 15)
      Publisher no.: 20-1891
    - Honeysuckle Rose [Side A] -- Blues [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Publisher no.: 25559
      Artists: Tommy Dorsey- Trombone, Bunny Berigen- Trumpet, Thomas "Fats" Waller- Piano, Dick McDonough- Guitar, George "Georgia" Wettling- Drums
    - You Won't Be Satisfied (Until You Break My Heart) [Side A] -- The Frim Fram Sauce [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Publisher no.: 23496
    - Swing You Cats [Side A] -- Snowball [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 18)
      Publisher no.: B-10225
    - Mood Indigo [Side A] -- Wall Street Wail [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 19)
      Publisher no.: 80003
    - I'm Crazy 'Bout My Baby (And My Baby's Crazy 'Bout Me) [Side A] -- Dragging My Heart Around [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Publisher no.: 279.749
    - My Honey's Loving' Arms [Side A] -- When My Sugar Walks Down the Street [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Publisher no.: 30-0801
    - Body and Soul [Side A] -- It Had to Be You [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Publisher no.: 30-0825
    - The Heebie Jeebies are Rockin' the Town [Side A] -- Gin for Christmas [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Publisher no.: 26423
    - Moonglow (Claro de Luna)[Side A] -- My Blue Heaven (Mi Cielo Azul) [Side B] (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Publisher no.: 27405
- Kelmer Gift, Series 8.
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 954)
- Walter Collection, Series 9.
  - Unprocessed Sound Discs (Box 679)
  - Unprocessed Sound Discs (Box 680)
  - Unprocessed Sound Discs (Box 681)
- Wolcott Gift, Series 10.
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 275)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 276)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 277)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 278)
  - Unprocessed Sound Recordings (Box 279)